1. startExistingApplication("com.kfc.mobile", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. delay(3, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
9. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Banner"), 0)
13. swipe(281, 800, 434, 61)
17. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Title - PROMOS AND REWARDS"), 0)
23. Get Device Height and Store in to device_height variable
29. Get Width Height and Store in to device_Width variable
35. Storing the value in startY variable by dividing device height by 2 Because Y coordinates are constant
41. Here startY and endY values are equal for Horizontal Swiping for that assigning startX value to endX
47. Storing the value in startX variable
53. Storing the value in endX variable
59. Here Y constant for Swipe Horizontal Right to Left
63. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/View All"), 3)
67. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Title - ONGOING PROMO"), 0)
71. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Promo List 1"), 0)
75. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Promo List 2"), 0)
79. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Promo List 3"), 0)
83. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Promo List 1"), 3)
87. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Button Back Promo Detail"), 3)
91. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Home Page/Promotion/Button Back"), 3)
95. delay(3, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
99. closeApplication()
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())