1. startExistingApplication("com.kfc.mobile", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. delay(5, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
9. swipe(281, 600, 434, 90)
15. Get Device Height and Store in to device_height variable
21. Get Width Height and Store in to device_Width variable
27. Storing the value in startY variable by dividing device height by 2 Because Y coordinates are constant
33. Here startY and endY values are equal for Horizontal Swiping for that assigning startX value to endX
39. Storing the value in startX variable
45. Storing the value in endX variable
51. Here Y constant for Swipe Horizontal Right to Left
55. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/Drive Thru/android.widget.TextView - DRIVE-THRU"), 5)
59. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Search KFC Outlet"), 5)
63. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Search KFC Outlet"), 0, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
67. setText(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/EditText - Search KFC Outlet"), "Kemang", 5)
71. hideKeyboard()
75. delay(5, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
79. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Button - Select Outlet"), 5)
83. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Button - Select Outlet"), 0)
87. delay(5, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
91. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/List Menu Group"), 5)
95. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/List Menu Group"), 5)
99. delay(3, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
103. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Breakfast"), 3)
107. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/List Menu Group"), 3)
111. delay(3, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
115. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Spesial"), 3)
119. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Button - Add"), 3)
123. delay(3, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
127. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/List Item Costum"), 5)
131. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Button - Continue Custom"), 5)
135. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Next Button Order"), 5)
139. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/You Got Free GOCENG"), 5)
143. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Continue Choose Reward"), 5)
147. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Continue Choose Reward"), 5)
151. setText(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/Drive Thru/Plat Number"), "B 4020 VYO", 0)
155. delay(5, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
159. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Button - Choose Now Reward"), 5)
163. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Button - Add Reward"), 5)
167. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Button - Confirm Reward"), 5)
171. swipe(281, 500, 434, 161)
175. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Select Payment Method"), 5)
179. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/PNP/Dine In/Group Payment Method"), 5)
183. tap(findTestObject("Productions/Create Order/Payment Method/Debit Card"), 5)
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())